<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<item><pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2017 00:22:57 +0300</pubDate><title><![CDATA[About us]]></title><url><![CDATA[o-nas_en]]></url><meta><![CDATA[]]></meta><metad><![CDATA[]]></metad><menuOrder><![CDATA[0]]></menuOrder><menuStatus><![CDATA[]]></menuStatus><template><![CDATA[template.php]]></template><content><![CDATA[&lt;hr /&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Capital Group&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Group of companies &quot;Capital&quot; has an almost 30-year experience in area of expertise and Advisory services at the international level. Competitive advantage is the knowledge of international standards, modern technologies and foreign languages. The company has extensive ties to most of the world&#039;s centers of business and Finance. &quot;Capital&quot; was involved in the creation of a number of financial institutions and stock exchanges in Russia(5) Russia(3), the international projects of the UN, EU, world Bank, Know how Fund.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Today the Group of companies &quot;Capital&quot;:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Provides management consulting and strategy development business development and crisis management of the economic entities of the Republic of Belarus and foreign companies;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Received membership in the Institute of professional management consultants (management) U.S. business, certificate in management CMC &quot;Certified Management Consultant&quot; with assignment of degree &quot;Master&quot;;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Has a Special certificate of the National Bank of the Republic of Belarus on the implementation of crisis management;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Professional participant of the securities market;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Performs exclusive financial intermediation;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Provides training and conducting international conferences and forums on investment and innovation, as well as seminars for professionals of various fields;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Is expert and consultant in international business and education;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Conducts research in the field of economy, international capital markets, cross-cultural communications;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;The initiator of creation of the world Trade Center in Minsk, allowing you to use a database more than 300 Centers in the world.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
]]></content><author><![CDATA[admin]]></author><parent><![CDATA[]]></parent><private><![CDATA[]]></private><menu><![CDATA[]]></menu></item>
